http://www.briankilmeade.com/privacy-policy

Radio/
Books/Sam Houston & The Alamo AvengersAndrew Jackson and the Miracle of New OrleansThomas Jefferson and the Tripoli PiratesGeorge Washington's Secret SixGeorge Washington's Secret Six Young ReadersOther Books
About/BioPhotosContact
Store/
BrianKilmeade.com
Privacy Policy
BrianKilmeade.com
Home/
Radio/
Books/Sam Houston & The Alamo AvengersAndrew Jackson and the Miracle of New OrleansThomas Jefferson and the Tripoli PiratesGeorge Washington's Secret SixGeorge Washington's Secret Six Young ReadersOther Books
About/BioPhotosContact
Store/
BrianKilmeade.com Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to us.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that BrianKilmeade.com collects, and the ways in which BrianKilmeade.com uses that personal information.BrianKilmeade.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: information about your use of this website, information about transactions carried out over this website, information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including Newsletter subscription through Mailchimp email); and any other information that you send to BrianKilmeade.com.BrianKilmeade.com may use your personal information to: administer this website, personalize the website for you, enable your access to and use of the website services, send you marketing communications.In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, BrianKilmeade.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.BrianKilmeade.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Personal information that you submit for publication on the website may be published on the internet and may be available around the world. You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information. BrianKilmeade.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.As you browse BrianKilmeade.com advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partners enable us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with BrianKilmeade.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  If you have any questions about this privacy policy or BrianKilmeade.com’s treatment of your personal information, please write by email to BrianKilmeade@BrianKilmeade.com.
Home/
Radio/
Books/Sam Houston & The Alamo AvengersAndrew Jackson and the Miracle of New OrleansThomas Jefferson and the Tripoli PiratesGeorge Washington's Secret SixGeorge Washington's Secret Six Young ReadersOther Books
About/BioPhotosContact
Store/
BrianKilmeade.com
Email Address
Sign Up
We respect your privacy.
Thank you!
Privacy Policy
